## Takata Kei

5-chōme-46-4 Yoyogi, Shibuya City, Tokyo 151-0053, Japan **goldone0101@gmail.com** 

#### Skills

HTML / CSS / SCSS, JAVASCRIPT / TYPESCRIPT, BOOTSTRAP, MERN, PHP / MYSQL, WEB3JS, ETHERJS, VUEJS, BLOCKCHAIN ARCHITECTURE, ETHEREUM-COMPATIBLE CHAINS, SOLIDITY, SMART CONTRACT, ETHEREUM PLATFORM, HARDHAT / TRUFFLE, CRYPTOCURRENCY, NFT, RUST, SOLANA, DAPP, INFURA

## Summary

This is Takata Kei from Japan and I have 7+ years of experience in web development.

Experienced full stack developer with a strong background in developing award-winning applications for a diverse clientele. 7+ years of industry experience includes programming, debugging, and wireframes.

My priority skills are solidity, dapp, web3 integration, JavaScript, Typescript, MERN, Python, PHP, AWS, rest API, Angular etc...

Senior blockchain developer with high skill and rich experience in blockchain, EVM, smart contract, NFT, solidity, cryptocurrency, tokenomics, dapp, defi, moralis, Infura etc...

Also, I handle tasks with accuracy and efficiency.

Furthermore, I have worked as a blockchain full stack developer in a previous company and very familiar with writing smart contract and UX/UI and developed many projects in this field.

As a developer, enjoy learning new technologies and sharing findings with my colleagues.

I have been actively working in software development since 2015, and an experienced senior developer with outstanding experience in various fields, such as web, mobile and Blockchain.

My major skills are blockchain-based web and mobile application development.

Currently, I am looking for a remote job. Not only that, but I am ready to start your project and will provide professional skills and results to you.

# Experience

#### Nov 2021 - Feb 2022

## Digitalax - BLOCKCHAIN FULL-STACK ENGINEER

- Built sophisticated smart contracts like staking marketplace offers, troubleshoot production issues, contributed to gas fee optimization, and deployed into Ethereum mainnet.
- Migrated smart contracts from Ethereum to Polygon and existing assets (NFTs, offers, collections) to newly deployed contracts on Polygon.
- Performed a Web3 integration with the smart contracts on Next.js.
- Built subgraph endpoints to interact with the smart contract triggered events and deploy them into the graph protocol.
- Worked closely with other protocols like Rarible, Aave, and Compound.

Technologies: Solidity, Ethereum, Polygon, Web3.js, Subgraph

#### Feb 2021 - Oct 2021

#### Escrow Protocol- BLOCKCHAIN FULL-STACK ENGINEER

- Built a front-end application for minting and staking NFTs using React and Web3.js.
- Contributed to a contract for NFT registration and redemption with Solidity.
- Created a POC Vue.js front-end platform for an NFT gallery using Moralis and Vue 3.
- Worked on the token distribution and migration from BSC to Polygon network using BscScan, PolygonScan API, and Solidity.

Technologies: Blockchain, Web3.js, Solidity, Ethers.js, Moralis, React, Vue.js, JavaScript

May 2020 - Jan 2021

Cave Consulting Inc - ANGULAR DEVELOPER

- Developed an Angular, RxJS, and Angular Material web app for managing user registration for seminars and webinars hosting in Firebase.
- Created a Node.js backend with Firebase cloud function and Firestore as the database while Google Storage was used as file storage.
- Took 100% responsibility for the project of planning, architecture, development, and deployment.

Technologies: Angular, Firebase, Node.js, JavaScript, Material-UI, Bootstrap, Google API

#### Jan 2019 - Mar 2020

#### Gelato Network - BLOCKCHAIN FULL-STACK ENGINEER

- Developed automated trading strategies on Uniswap and QuickSwap.
- Built smart contract with solidity and deployed using Truffle.
- Used Flashbots API to fetch block info regarding trading pool and staking.
- Worked on building trading view, swap modal using React, Next, TypeScript, Webs.is, and Subgraph.
- Supported limit orders on the Ethereum Mainnet and Polygon (Matic).

Technologies: Web3.js, Solidity, Blockchain, Ethers.js, React, Ethereum, JavaScript

#### Aug 2016 - Oct 2018

#### Holidu - FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

- Integrated Redux and MobX on a number of React-based front-end projects for the better state management of React components.
- Implemented a GraphQL-and-Apollo server for a React-and-Vue.js front-end data query.
- Built AWS Lambda functions with Node.js and configured an automated Git's pulling and deploying pipeline in AWS using Nginx, PM2, and Bitbucket webhooks.
- Created a new customized chart library using D3.js and Plotly.js.

- Embedded a Google tag manager and Google Analytics for the website conversion tracking and the user event tracking.
- Integrated Vue.js, Vuex, and Vuetify with a Laravel back-end.

Technologies: AWS Lambda, GraphQL, Node.js, Vue.js, React, PHP, JavaScript

## May 2015 - Jun 2016

### Theme Paradise - FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

- Worked on part-time engagement for the building of several responsive multi-purpose WordPress themes.
- Built my WordPress theme framework called Crystal.
- Utilized my strong experience with building WordPress shortcodes along with Visual Composer.

Technologies: jQuery, JavaScript, WordPress, PHP

#### Education

#### 2011 - 2015

# The University of Tokyo

BACHELOR'S DEGREE OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

#### **Contact Me**

Skype: live:.cid.abecc0e8069e6d36

Email: goldone0101@gmail.com

Location: 5-chōme-46-4 Yoyogi, Shibuya City, Tokyo 151-0053, Japan